http://www.subesports.com/privacy-policy

SubÉ Sports Internet Privacy Policy
Sube Sports respects the privacy of individuals who visit our Web site, http://www.subesports.com/, and is committed to protecting your online personal information in accordance with the terms of this Internet Privacy Policy.
While you can use many features of our Web site without being required to provide personally identifiable information, you may be requested to provide your personal information to gain access to some of our content or services, to contact us, or to receive additional information from us. By visiting http://www.subesports.com/, you accept and agree to the practices described in this Internet Privacy Policy.
How We Collect and Use Personal Information
We may collect personal information about you when you visit http://www.subesports.com/, which may give you the ability to access additional features on our Web site and our online services. This information is used to provide you with the information that you are requesting from us, access to our services and data and information regarding the services we provide to you and/or your customers. Personal information we collect may include: your login ID and password, your name, your company name, your mailing address, your e-mail address, your phone number, your fax number and additional information used to contact you.
Automatic Information
We may also collect automatic information about your visit to our Web site, such as time of day, browser type and version, browser language, your operating system and platform, and the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet. This information is used for analytical purposes and to help us provide services to our clients. We may also use this information to administer and troubleshoot our Web site and servers.
How We Protect Your Personal Information
We have taken precautions to protect your personal information under our control from misuse, loss or alteration. Our security measures include industry standard technology and equipment to help protect your data. Unfortunately, however, no system can ensure complete security and you should take all necessary steps to protect your information and its transmission to us. Since the Internet is a public medium, we cannot guarantee the protection of your personal information.
How We Use "Cookies"
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that some Web sites store on your computer's hard drive when you visit them. Like many other Web sites, we may use cookies to identify users and their preferences for our business purposes.
What We Provide to Third-Parties
Third-party agents may need access to some of your personal information. For example, we may need to share your name and address with your employer, government regulators, or our service providers. In such cases, we only provide third-party agents with the minimum amount of information needed to complete the requested service or transaction. We may also provide your information to our affiliated companies and successors.
We reserve the right to provide third-parties with aggregate statistics about our clients, traffic patterns, and related site information. This data reflects site usage patterns, but does not contain personally identifiable information about any individual user.
Linked Web Sites
We may provide links to third-party sites. Because we do not control these Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these third-party Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such Web sites or the information collected on such Web sites.
Obtaining Your Consent
By using our Web site, you authorize us to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user. This information will be used for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. If you register as a user of our site, you authorize us to use this to personalize the information that we deliver to you. As a registered site user, you give us and our agents permission to send you e-mails or place phone calls to you related to the information that you request.
Children's Privacy
We do not provide services to children. In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we do not knowingly request or solicit personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. In the event that we receive actual knowledge that we have collected such personal information without the requisite and verifiable parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as is practical.
California Privacy
Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits individuals who are California residents to request certain information regarding the disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to sales@subesports.com.
Compliance with Legal Process
Please be aware that we will release specific personal information about you if required to do so to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute or court order. We may also choose to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, but are not under any obligation to do so.
Policy Updates
We may change this privacy policy at any time in our sole discretion. Any updates to our privacy policy will be posted on this page, so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Continued use of the site following our posting of the change notice or an updated privacy policy will constitute binding acceptance of those changes.
JOIN OUR MAILING LIST AND GET SPECIAL OFFERSFor Email Newsletters you can trust.
Copyright 2001-2020 Subé Sports All Rights Reserved.
Terms and Conditions | Privacy Policy
17161 Palmdale Ln. Huntington Beach, Ca 92647info@subesports.com
